AFL-CIO Railway Employees' Department Records 5478
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series XII: Political Matters - Correspondence, Campaign Material and Minutes Relevant of the National Congressional Election, 1932-1965
  - Elections - Colorado, 1944-1948 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    Code No. 33-147; Feb. 1, 1944 - Feb. 19, 1948
  - Elections - Connecticut, 1944-1946 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    Code No. 33-147; Sept. 28, 1944 - Oct. 16, 1946
  - Elections - Delaware, 1944-1946 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    Code No. 33-147; Sept. 14, 1944 - Oct. 4, 1946
  - Elections - Florida, 1944-1946 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    Code No. 33-147; Mar. 31, 1944 - Sept. 3, 1946
  - Elections - Georgia, 1943-1946 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    Code No. 33-147; Oct. 13, 1943 - Sept. 3, 1946
  - Elections - Idaho, 1944-1946 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    Code No. 33-147; May 5, 1944 - Sept. 3, 1946
  - Elections - Illinois, 1943-1947 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    Code No. 33-147; Jul. 3, 1943 - Jan. 17, 1947
  - Elections - Indiana, 1944-1946 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    Code No. 33-147; Mar. 27, 1944 - Sept. 3, 1946
  - Elections - Iowa, 1944-1947 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    Code No. 33-147; Apr. 20, 1944 - May 27, 1947
  - Elections - Kansas, 1944-1946 (Box 37, Folder 17)
    Code No. 33-147; May 31, 1944 - Oct. 16, 1946
  - Elections - Kentucky, 1944-1947 (Box 37, Folder 18)
    Code No. 33-147; Jun. 14, 1944 - Nov. 10, 1947
  - Elections - Louisiana, 1944-1948 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    Code No. 33-147; Jun. 26, 1944 - Aug. 4, 1948
  - Elections - Maine, 1942-1946 (Box 37, Folder 20)
    Code No. 33-147; May 28, 1942 - Aug. 22, 1946
  - Elections - Maryland, 1944-1946 (Box 37, Folder 21)
    Code No. 33-147; May 18, 1944 - Oct. 15, 1946
  - Elections - Massachusetts, 1944-1947 (Box 37, Folder 22)
    Code No. 33-147; Jun. 12, 1944 - Oct. 10, 1947
  - Elections - Michigan, 1944-1947 (Box 37, Folder 23)
    Code No. 33-147; May 19, 1944 - Jul. 28, 1947
  - Elections - Minnesota, 1944-1946 (Box 37, Folder 24)
    Code No. 33-147; May 22, 1944 - Oct. 16, 1946
  - Elections - Mississippi, 1944-1946 (Box 37, Folder 25)
    Code No. 33-147; Jun. 5, 1944 - Oct. 16, 1946
  - Elections - Missouri, 1944-1946 (Box 37, Folder 26)
    Code No. 33-147; Jun. 14, 1944 - Oct. 28, 1946
  - Elections - Montana, 1944-1946 (Box 37, Folder 27)
    Code No. 33-147; May 22, 1944 - Oct. 17, 1946
  - Elections - Nebraska, 1944-1946 (Box 37, Folder 28)
    Code No. 33-147; Mar. 15, 1944 - Oct. 16, 1946
  - Elections - Nevada, 1944-1946 (Box 37, Folder 29)
    Code No. 33-147; Jun. 21, 1944 - Oct. 23, 1946]
  - Elections - New Hampshire, 1944-1946 (Box 37, Folder 30)
    Code No. 33-147; May 31, 1944 - Sept. 10, 1946
  - Elections - New Jersey, 1944-1948 (Box 37, Folder 31)
    Code No. 33-147 Apr. 7, 1944 - Mar. 16, 1948
  - Elections - New Mexico, 1944-1946 (Box 37, Folder 32)
    Code No. 33-147; May 11, 1944 - Oct. 15, 1946
  - Elections - New York, 1944-1946 (Box 37, Folder 33)
    Code No. 33-147; May 18, 1944 - Oct. 16, 1946
  - Elections - North Carolina, 1943-1946 (Box 37, Folder 34)
    Code No. 33-147 Dec. 7, 1943 - Sept. 12, 1946
  - Elections - North Dakota, 1944-1946 (Box 37, Folder 35)
    Code No. 33-147; Apr. 11, 1944 - Oct. 4, 1946
  - Elections - Ohio, 1942-1946 (Box 37, Folder 36)
    Code No. 33-147, pt. 2; Nov. 12, 1942 - Nov. 21, 1946
  - Elections - Oklahoma, 1944-1946 (Box 37, Folder 37)
    Code No. 33-147; May 25, 1944 - Oct. 4, 1946
  - Elections - Oregon, 1944-1946 (Box 37, Folder 38)
    Code No. 33-147; Mar. 11, 1944 - Oct. 15, 1946
  - Elections - Pennsylvania, 1943-1947 (Box 37, Folder 39)
    Code No. 33-147; Oct. 1, 1943 - Sept. 2, 1947
  - Elections - Rhode Island, 1944-1946 (Box 37, Folder 40)
    Code No. 33-147; Sept. 20, 1944 - Oct. 15, 1946
  - Elections - South Carolina, 1941-1946 (Box 37, Folder 41)
    Code No. 33-147; Oct. 16, 1941 - Sept. 10, 1946
  - Elections - South Dakota, 1944-1946 (Box 37, Folder 42)
    Code No. 33-147; Mar. 20, 1944 - Oct. 15, 1946
  - Elections - Tennessee, 1943-1947 (Box 37, Folder 43)
    Code No. 33-147; Jan. 20, 1943 - Aug. 8, 1947
  - Elections - Texas, 1944-1948 (Box 37, Folder 44)
    Code No. 33-147; Jun. 2, 1944 - Feb. 27, 1948
  - Elections - Utah, 1942-1946 (Box 37, Folder 45)
    Code No. 33-147; Oct. 24, 1942 - Dec. 5, 1946
  - Elections - Vermont, 1944-1946 (Box 37, Folder 46)
    Code No. 33-147; Jan. 19, 1944 - Sept. 12, 1946
  - Elections - Virginia, 1944-1946 (Box 37, Folder 47)
    Code No. 33-147; Aug. 2, 1944 - Oct. 15, 1946
  - Elections - Washington, 1944-1947 (Box 37, Folder 48)
    Code No. 33-147; Oct. 18, 1944 - Jun. 3, 1947
  - Elections - West Virginia, 1946 (Box 37, Folder 49)
    Code No. 33-147; Jun. 18, 1946 - Oct. 16, 1946
  - Elections - Wisconsin, 1946-1947 (Box 37, Folder 50)
    Code No. 33-147; Jun. 17, 1946 - Mar. 7, 1947
  - Elections - Wyoming, 1946 (Box 37, Folder 51)
    Code No. 33-147; Jun. 11, 1946 - Oct. 22, 1946
  - Railway Labor's Political League, 1950-1956 (Box 37, Folder 52)
    Code No. 33-158, Sec. I; Oct. 1950 - Aug. 20, 1956
  - Railway Labor's Political League, 1947-1952 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    Code No. 33-158; Dec. 6, 1947 - Jul. 24, 1952
  - Railway Labor's Political League, 1952-1960 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    Code No. 33-158; Aug. 12, 1952 - Sept. 23, 1960
  - Labor's League for Political Education, 1947-1953 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    Code No. 33-159; Dec. 12, 1947 - Jul. 1, 1953
  - Labor's League for Political Education, 1953-1965 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    Code No. 33-159, pt. 2; Jul. 24, 1953 - Feb. 25, 1965
- Series XIII: Transportation Act, 1921-1928
  Correspondence (carbons and originals), reports, petitions, and published legislative materials regarding hearings before the Senate Committee on Interstate Commerce Commission; testimony of labor leaders, businessmen and other concerned parties on the Ho
  - Transportation Act - Amendments, 1921-1923 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    Code No. 25-26; Mar. 3, 1921 - Dec. 31, 1923
  - Transportation Act - Amendments, 1923-1924 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    Code No. 35-26, pt. 2; Dec. 21, 1923 - Nov. 15, 1924
  - Transportation Act - Potter Plan, 1925 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    Code No. 35-26-A; Jul. 29, 1925
- Series XIV: Interstate Commerce Commission, 1923-1966
  Correspondence (carbons and originals), reports, petitions, and legal documents regarding RED request that ICC require railroads to comply with inspection and safety rules; carrier petitions seeking exemptions from certain provisions and rules for the ins
  - ICC - Rules and Instructions for inspection of locomotives other than steam, 1925-1951 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    Code No. 35-33, Subj. 3; Apr. 1, 1925 - Jul. 3, 1951
  - ICC - Rules and Instructions for inspection of locomotives other than steam, 1951-1954 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    Code No. 35-33, Subj. 3, pt. 2; Feb. 2, 1951 - Nov. 30, 1954
  - ICC - Rules and Instructions for inspection of locomotives other than steam, 1954-1955 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    Code No. 35-33, Subj. 3, pt. 3; Nov. 22, 1954 - Jul. 28, 1955
  - ICC - Rules and Instructions for inspection of locomotives other than steam, 1955-1957 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    Code No. 35-33, Subj. 3, pt. 4; Aug. 1, 1955 - May 27, 1957
  - ICC - Rules and Instructions for inspection of locomotives other than steam, 1957-1960 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    Code No. 35-33, Subj. 3, pt. 5; Jul. 12, 1957 - Jun. 30, 1960
  - ICC - Rules and Instructions for inspection of locomotives other than steam, 1960-1964 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    Code No. 35-33, Subj. 3, pt. 6; Jun. 2, 1960 - Aug. 28, 1964
  - ICC - Rules and Instructions for inspection of locomotives other than steam, 1964-1966 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    Code No. 35-33, Subj. 3, pt. 7; Sept. 14, 1964 - Aug. 30, 1966
  - Increased Railway Rates, Fares and Charges, 1937-1946 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    Code No. 35-39, pt. 2; Nov. 7, 1937 - Dec. 13, 1946
  - Increased Railway Rates, Fares and Charges, 1947-1958 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    Code No. 35-39, pt. 3; Aug. 24, 1947 - Dec. 10, 1958
  - Railroad Passenger Train Deficit Investigation, 1959-1961 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    Code No. 35-39, pt. 4; Jan. 14, 1959 - Jun. 20, 1961
  - Federal Employers' Liability Law, 1923-1955 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    Code No. 35-50; Dec. 18, 1923 - Oct. 18, 1955
  - Ex Parte 72 RE: Subordinate Officials, Craft or Class, 1941-1952 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    Code No. 35-56, pt. 2; May 28, 1941 - Dec. 19, 1952
- Series XXVIII: Correspondence RE: Board of Adjustments, 1923-1946
  Includes records relating to the National Shop Craft Agreements, work rules, Railroad Retirement Board rules and rulings and representational disputes, c., 1922-1965. Files are arranged by carrier name.
  - Western Region, 1926-1930 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    Code No. 35-63-A; Jun. 1, 1926 - May 9, 1930
  - American Railway Express, 1926-1934 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    Code No. 35-63-1; Jul. 7, 1926 - Jul. 16, 1934
  - Chicago Great Western Railroad, 1923-1934 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    Code No. 35-63-A-1; Apr. 12, 1923 - Aug. 2, 1934
  - Chicago, Milwaukee and Saint Paul Railroad, 1926-1934 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    Code No. 35-63-A-2; Jun. 8, 1926 - Jun. 16, 1934
  - Chicago Northwestern Railroad, 1926-1933 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    Code No. 35-63-A-3; Jul. 13, 1926 - Nov. 13, 1933
  - Chicago, Peoria and St. Louis Railroad, 1926-1946 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    Code No. 35-63-A-4; Jul. 13, 1926 - Aug. 24, 1946
  - Chicago, St. Paul, Minneapolis and Omaha Railroad, 1926-1929 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    Code No. 35-63-A-5; Jun. 4, 1926 - Nov. 4, 1929
  - Copper Range Railroad, 1926 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    Code No. 35-63-A-6; Jul. 13, 1926 - Jul. 20, 1926
  - Davenport, Rock Island and Northwestern Railroad, 1926 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    Code No. 35-63-A-7; Jul. 13, 1926 - Sept. 27, 1926
  - Des Moines Union Railroad, 1926 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    Code No. 35-63-A-8; Jul. 13, 1926 - Dec. 1, 1926
  - Duluth, South Shore and Atlantic Railroad and Mineral Range Railroad, 1926 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    Code No. 35-63-A-9; Jun. 4, 1926 - Nov. 12, 1926
  - Duluth, Winnipeg and Pacific Railroad, 1926 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    Code No. 35-63-A-10; Jun. 4, 1926 - Dec. 18, 1926
  - Munsing, Marquette and Southeastern Railroad, 1926 (Box 41, Folder 18)
    Code No. 35-63-A-11; Jun. 4, 1926 - Nov. 8, 1926
  - Elgin, Joliet and Eastern Railroad, 1926-1933 (Box 41, Folder 19)
    Code No. 35-63-A-12; Jun. 12, 1926 - Dec. 19, 1933
  - Fort Dodge, Des Moines and Southern Railroad, 1926-1927 (Box 41, Folder 20)
    Code No. 35-63-A-14; Jul. 13, 1926 - Aug. 26, 1927
  - Green Bay Western Railroad, 1926-1927 (Box 41, Folder 21)
    Code No. 35-63-A-15; Jun. 30, 1926 - Feb. 7, 1927
  - Louisiana and Arkansas Railroad, 1926 (Box 41, Folder 22)
    Code No. 35-63-A-16; Jul. 13, 1926 - Sept. 11, 1926
  - New Orleans Public Belt Railroad, 1926 (Box 41, Folder 23)
    Code No. 35-63-A-17; Jul. 13, 1926 - Sept. 14, 1926
  - Pere Marquette Railroad, 1934 (Box 41, Folder 24)
    Code No. 35-63-A-18; Jul. 25, 1934 - Jul. 26, 1934
  - St. Louis Short Lines Railroad, 1926 (Box 41, Folder 25)
    Code No. 35-63-A-20; Jul. 13, 1926 - Oct. 29, 1926
  - St. Louis Terminal Railroad, 1926 (Box 41, Folder 26)
    Code No. 35-63-A-21; May 22, 1926 - Oct. 29, 1926
  - Switching and Terminal Lines of Chicago, 1926 (Box 41, Folder 27)
    Code No. 35-63-A-22; Jul. 13, 1926 - Dec. 4, 1926
  - Tonopah and Tidewater Railroad, 1926 (Box 41, Folder 28)
    Code No. 35-63-A-23; Jul. 13, 1926 - Nov. 11, 1926
  - Western Pacific Railroad, 1926 (Box 41, Folder 29)
    Code No. 35-63-A-24; Jul. 13, 1926 - Nov. 10, 1926
  - St. Paul Bridge and Terminal Railroad, 1926 (Box 41, Folder 30)
    Code No. 35-63-A-25; Jun. 4, 1926 - Nov. 5, 1926
  - Minneapolis and St. Paul Railroad, 1926 (Box 41, Folder 31)
    Code No. 35-63-A-26; Jun. 4, 1926 - Oct. 29, 1926
  - Minneapolis and International Falls Railroad, 1926 (Box 41, Folder 32)
    Code No. 35-63-A-27; Jun. 4, 1926 - Nov. 16, 1926
  - Duluth, Missabe and Northern Railroad, 1926 (Box 41, Folder 33)
    Code No. 35-63-A-28; Jun. 4, 1926 - Jun. 12, 1926
  - Union Pacific Railroad, 1930 (Box 41, Folder 34)
    Code No. 35-63-A-30; Jul. 8, 1930
  - Minneapolis, Northfield and Southern Railway, Minnesota Western Railway Co. and Electric Short Line Terminal Co. - National Adjustment Boards, 1934 (Box 41, Folder 35)
    Code No. 35-63-A-31; Jul. 13, 1934 - Aug. 29, 1934
  - Gulf Coast Lines Railroad, 1934 (Box 41, Folder 36)
    Code No. 35-63-A-32; Aug. 7, 1934
  - Northern Pacific Railroad, 1934 (Box 41, Folder 37)
    Code No. 35-63-A-33; Jul. 21, 1934 - Aug. 4, 1934
  - Eastern Region, 1926-1933 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    Code No. 35-63-B; Jun. 1, 1926 - Apr. 20, 1933
  - Akron-Canton and Youngstown Railway Co., 1926 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    Code No. 35-63-B-1; Jul. 13, 1926 - Nov. 8, 1926
  - Ann Arbor Railroad, 1926 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    Code No. 35-63-B-2; Jul. 7, 1926 - Sept. 18, 1926
  - Baltimore and Ohio Railroad, 1926-1932 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    Code No. 35-63-B-3; Jul. 13, 1926 - Apr. 29, 1932
  - Big Four (C.C.C. & St. Louis), 1926-1929 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    Code No. 35-63-B-4; Jun. 5, 1926 - Oct. 3, 1929
  - Buffalo, Rochester and Pittsburgh Railroad, 1926 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    Code No. 35-63-B-5; Jul. 13, 1926 - Dec. 1, 1926
  - Buffalo and Susquehanna Railroad, 1926 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    Code No. 35-63-B-6; Jul. 13, 1926 - Nov. 19, 1926
  - Cumberland and Pennsylvania Railroad, 1926 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    Code No. 35-63-B-7; Jul. 13, 1926 - Nov. 11, 1926
  - Chicago, Indianapolis and Louisville Railroad, 1926 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    Code No. 35-63-B-8; Jun. 21, 1926 - Oct. 21, 1926
  - Detroit and Mackinac Railroad, 1926 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    Code No. 35-63-B-9; Jul. 13, 1926 - Nov. 15, 1926
  - Erie Railroad, 1926-1927 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    Code No. 35-63-B-10; Jul. 13, 1926 - Jan. 14, 1927
  - Grand Trunk Western, 1926 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    Code No. 35-63-B-11; Jul. 13, 1926 - Nov. 3, 1926
  - Hocking Valley Railroad, 1926-1929 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    Code No. 35-63-B-12; Jun. 7, 1926 - May 15, 1929
  - Hudson and Manhattan Railroad, 1926-1927 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    Code No. 35-63-B-13; Jul. 18, 1926 - Jan. 6, 1927
  - Lehigh and Hudson River Railroad, 1926 (Box 42, Folder 15)
    Code No. 35-63-B-14; Jul. 13, 1926 - Nov. 11, 1926
  - New York Central Railroad, 1926-1931 (Box 42, Folder 16)
    Code No. 35-63-B-15; Jun. 9, 1926 - Sept. 2, 1931
  - Toledo Terminal Railroad, 1926 (Box 42, Folder 17)
    Code No. 35-63-B-16; Jul. 13, 1926 - Oct. 8, 1926
  - Ulster and Delaware Railroad, 1926 (Box 42, Folder 18)
    Code No. 35-63-B-17; Jul. 13, 1926 - Sept. 13, 1926
  - Michigan Central Railroad, 1926 (Box 42, Folder 19)
    Code No. 35-63-B-18; Jul. 7, 1926 - Sept. 22, 1926
  - Boston and Albany Railroad, 1926 (Box 42, Folder 20)
    Code No. 35-63-B-19; Jul. 7, 1926 - Oct. 14, 1926
  - Pittsburgh and Lake Erie Railroad, 1926 (Box 42, Folder 21)
    Code No. 35-63-B-20; Jul. 7, 1926 - Sept. 13, 1926
  - Southeastern Region, 1926-1930 (Box 42, Folder 22)
    Code No. 35-63-C; Jun. 1, 1926 - Mar. 17, 1930
  - Alabama, Tennessee and Northern Railroad, 1926 (Box 42, Folder 23)
    Code No. 35-63-C-1; Jul. 13, 1926 - Sept. 23, 1926
  - Carolina, Clinchfield and Ohio Railroad, 1926 (Box 42, Folder 24)
    Code No. 35-63-C-2; Jul. 7, 1926 - Oct. 9, 1926
  - Chesapeake and Ohio Railroad, 1926-1931 (Box 42, Folder 25)
    Code No. 35-63-C-3; Jul. 1, 1926 - May 2, 1931
  - Georgia, Florida and Alabama Railroad, 1926 (Box 42, Folder 26)
    Code No. 35-63-C-4; Jul. 13, 1926 - Nov. 11, 1926
  - Macon, Dublin and Savannah Railroad, 1926-1934 (Box 42, Folder 27)
    Code No. 35-63-C-5; Jun. 24, 1926 - Nov. 11, 1926
  - Seaboard Air Line Railroad, 1926-1934 (Box 42, Folder 28)
    Code No. 35-63-C-6; Jul. 6, 1926 - Jul. 25, 1934
  - Southern and Allied Lines Railroad, 1926-1934 (Box 42, Folder 29)
    Code No. 35-63-C-7; Jul. 6, 1926 - Jul. 25, 1934
  - Mobile and Ohio Railroad, 1926-1934 (Box 42, Folder 30)
    Code No. 35-63-C-8; Jul. 13, 1926 - Aug. 10, 1934
  - Tennessee Central Railroad, 1926-1930 (Box 42, Folder 31)
    Code No. 35-63-C-9; Jul. 13, 1926 - Aug. 19, 1930
  - New Orleans-Great Northern Railroad, 1926 (Box 42, Folder 32)
    Code No. 35-63-C-10; Jul. 13, 1926 - Sept. 23, 1926
  - Norfolk and Southern Railroad, 1934 (Box 42, Folder 33)
    Code No. 35-63-C-11; Jul. 27, 1934
  - Louisville and Nashville Railroad, 1941 (Box 42, Folder 34)
    Code No. 35-63-C-12; May 12, 1941 - May 19, 1941
  - Atlanta, Birmingham and Coast Railroad, 1941-1942 (Box 42, Folder 35)
    Code No. 35-63-C-13; Jan. 5, 1941 - Jan. 9, 1942
  - Southwestern Region, 1927-1928 (Box 42, Folder 36)
    Code No. 35-63-D; Jan. 3, 1927 - Apr. 4, 1928
  - Misc. - Memo in support of proposed amendments to the Railway Labor Act (Box 42, Folder 37)
- Series XV: Railway Labor Act, 1926-1964
  Correspondence (carbons and originals), case files, minutes, legal documents, pamphlets, clippings, and statistical data regarding the activities of the U.S. National Mediation Board; law suits brought before the National Railroad Adjustment Board; Suprem
  - Proposed Amendments to the Railway Labor Act, 1928-1937 (Box 42, Folder 38)
    Code No. 35-64-Comm; Jan. 11, 1928 - May 27, 1937
  - Amendments to the Railway Labor Act, 1933-1934 (Box 42, Folder 39)
    Code No. 35-64-Comm, pt. 2; Dec. 14, 1933 - May 31, 1934
  - Amendments to the Railway Labor Act, 1934-1941 (Box 42, Folder 40)
    Code No. 35-64-Comm, pt. 3; Jun. 1, 1934 - Sept. 5, 1941
  - Med. Bd. - Dismissals (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Med. Bd. - Findings Upon Investigations (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Med. Bd. - Notice of Hearings (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Withdrawals - Investigations (Box 46, Folder 4)
    Code No. 35-64-8-1
  - File Copies of "Report to the President by the Emergency Board", 1920-1951 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    Code No. 35-64-10
  - Stabilization of Employment Program at meeting of 21 Chief Executives - Minutes, 1932 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Code No. 35-75; Jan. 13 - Feb. 1, 1932
  - Stabilization of Employment Questionnaire - Official Roster, 1930 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Code No. 35-76; May 15, 1930 - May 22, 1930
  - Stabilization of Employment, 1928-1931 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Code No. 35-76, pt. 1; Apr. 25, 1928 - Feb. 24, 1931
  - Stabilization of Employment, 1931 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    Code No. 35-76, pt. 2; Jan. 3, 1931 - Jun. 29, 1931
  - Stabilization of Employment, 1931-1932 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    Code No. 35-76, pt. 3; Jul. 2, 1931 - Jul. 5, 1932
  - Stabilization of Employment, 1932-1937 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    Code No. 35-76, pt. 4; Jul. 5, 1932 - Dec. 16, 1937
- Series XVI: Federal Affairs - Consolidation, Retirements, Pensions, ICC, Waterways, Ex Parte 171, Emergency Railway Legislation, etc., 1928-1970
  Correspondence (carbons and originals), legal documents, legislative materials, reports/studies, and clippings regarding legislative attempts to suspend ICC railroad consolidation; proposed pension systems for railroad employees and the evaluation of thes
  - Consolidation of Railroads, 1928-1931 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Code No. 35-80, pt. 1; Aug. 2, 1928 - Nov. 19, 1931
  - Consolidation of Railroads, 1932-1936 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    Code No. 35-80, pt. 2; Feb. 17, 1932 - Jun. 12, 1936
  - Pension Legislation, 1929-1931 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    Code No. 35-90, pt. 1; Apr. 24, 1929 - Oct. 30, 1931
  - Pension and Retirement Plans, 1939-1940 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    Code No. 35-90
  - Approved list of employers and index (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Pensions, 1931-1932 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    Code No. 35-90, pt. 2; Nov. 1, 1931 - Apr. 29, 1932
  - Pensions, 1932-1933 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    Code No. 35-90, pt. 3; May 2, 1932 - Apr. 27, 1933
  - Pensions, 1933-1934 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    Code No. 35-90, pt. 4; May 19, 1933 - Sept. 28, 1934
  - Retirement Act, 1934-1935 (Box 49a, Folder 1)
    Code No. 35-90, pt. 5; Oct. 3, 1934 - Jun. 25, 1935
  - Retirement Act, 1935-1936 (Box 49a, Folder 2)
    Code No. 35-90, pt. 6; Jun. 27, 1935 - Mar. 30, 1936
  - Retirement Act, 1936 (Box 49a, Folder 3)
    Code No. 35-90, pt. 7; Mar. 31, 1936 - Dec. 31, 1936
  - Retirement, 1937 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    Code No. 35-90, pt. 8; Jan. 1, 1937 - Aug. 10, 1937
  - Retirement, 1969-1970 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    Code No. 35-90, pt. 46; Oct. 16, 1969 - May 4, 1970
  - Special Pension Committee, 1938-1939 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    Code No. 35-90, Comm., pt. 1; Nov. 14, 1938 - Apr. 24, 1939
  - Amendments to Retirement Act, 1939-1941 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    Code No. 35-90, Comm., pt. 2, folder 1; May 5, 1939 - Jan. 31, 1941
  - Amendments to Retirement Act, 1941-1944 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    Code No. 35-90, Comm., pt. 2, folder 2; Feb. 5, 1941 - Apr. 26, 1944
  - Outside Bills Re: Retirement, 1948-1952 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    Code No. 35-90, O.B., pt. 3; Apr. 1948 - Feb. 6, 1952
  - Accident Reports Re: Accident Bulletins, 1925-1960 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    Code No. 35-94, pt. 1; Aug. 13, 1925 - Dec. 27, 1960
  - Appointments to ICC, 1929-1953 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    Code No. 35-95; Aug. 1, 1929 - Sept. 25, 1953
  - Appointments to ICC, 1954-1965 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    Code No. 35-95, pt. 2; Aug. 19, 1954 - May 25, 1965
  - Public Policies - Forms of Transportation other than railroads, 1949-1951 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    Code No. 35-100, pt. 1; Jan. 6, 1949 - Aug. 1, 1951
  - Federal Workman's Compensation Act for Railroad Employees, 1938-1941 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    Code No. 35-107-A, pt. 1; Apr. 20, 1938 - Dec. 30, 1941
  - Appointments to Government Positions, 1928-1941 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    Code No. 35-110, pt. 1; Dec. 20, 1928 - Dec. 29, 1941
  - Appointments to Government Positions, 1942-1964 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    Code No. 35-110, pt. 2; Jan. 8, 1942 - Dec. 29, 1964
  - Congressional Record on Appointment of Judge Parker (Box 52, Folder 2)
    Code No. 35-110-General
  - Deep Water Way - St. Lawrence River, Ohio River and Lake Erie, 1929-1939 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    Code No. 35-112, pt. 1; Aug. 22, 1929 - Feb. 27, 1939
  - Deep Water Way - St. Lawrence River, Ohio River and Lake Erie, 1939-1941 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    Code No. 35-112, pt. 2; Feb. 16, 1939 - Jun. 19, 1941
  - Deep Water Way - St. Lawrence River, Ohio River and Lake Erie, 1941-1945 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    Code No. 35-112, pt. 3; Jul. 2, 1941 - Dec. 26, 1945
  - Deep Water Way - St. Lawrence River, Ohio River and Lake Erie, 1946-1962 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    Code No. 35-112, pt. 4; Jan. 30, 1946 - Nov. 26, 1962
  - Interstate Commerce Commission - Ex Parte No. 171, 1931-1952 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    Code No. 35-127; Oct. 19, 1931 - Dec. 10, 1952; Rules, Standards and Instructions for Installation, Inspection, Maintenance and Repair of Automatic Block Signal Systems, etc.
  - Interstate Commerce Commission - Ex Parte No. 171, 1953-1960 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    Code No. 35-127, pt. 2; Jan. 2, 1953 - Aug. 31, 1960; Rules, Standards and Instructions for Installation, Inspection, Maintenance and Repair of Automatic Block Signal Systems, etc.
  - Interstate Commerce Commission - Ex Parte No. 171, 1960-1964 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    Code No. 35-127, pt. 3; Sept. 21, 1960 - May 4, 1964; Rules, Standards and Instructions for Installation, Inspection, Maintenance and Repair of Automatic Block Signal Systems, etc.
  - Application for Relief from the Requirements of Ex Parte 171 - A-C, 1931-1956 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    Code No. 35-127
  - Application for Relief from the Requirements of Ex Parte 171 - D-M, 1931-1956 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Application for Relief from the Requirements of Ex Parte 171 - N-R, 1931-1956 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Application for Relief from the Requirements of Ex Parte 171 - S-Z, 1931-1956 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Application for Relief from the Requirements of Ex Parte 171 - A-D, 1959-1960 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    Code No. 35-127; Mar. 23, 1959 - Sept. 28, 1960
  - Application for Relief from the Requirements of Ex Parte 171 - A-G, 1961-1964 (Box 54, Folder 2)